Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Director's Files, 1905-2013
  - Topical Files, 1905-1999
    - 1905-1950
      - Victoria University (Toronto), 1910-1935 (Box 49)
      - Victoria University College (New Zealand), 1934-1937 (Box 49)
      - Victory Book Campaign, 1941-1943 (Box 49)
      - Vienna National Library, 1934-1940 (Box 49)
      - Vignaud Library
        - 1912-1921 (Box 49)
        - 1922 (Box 49)
        - 1923-1926 (Box 49)
      - Virginia State Library, 1926-1930 (Box 49)
      - Virginia University
        - 1908-1925 (Box 49)
        - 1926-1937 (Box 49)
        - 1937-1944 (Box 49)
        - 1946-1950 (Box 49)
      - Visitors
        - 1926-1938 (Box 49)
        - 1938-1945 (Box 49)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 49)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 50)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 50)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 50)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 50)
      - Visitors Day
        - 1929-1932 (Box 50)
        - 1932-1934 (Box 50)
        - 1934-1936 (Box 50)
      - Vocational Conference, 1916-1917 (Box 50)
      - Vollbehr, Otto H.F., 1926-1934 (Box 50)
      - Wales National Library, 1921-1939 (Box 50)
      - Walker, Bryant, 1910-1931 (Box 50)
      - Walker, C.I., papers, 1926-1927 (Box 50)
      - Wants, 1943-1950 (Box 50)
      - War Information Centers, 1941-1942 (Box 50)
      - Warren, Edward K., Foundation, 1929-1930 (Box 50)
      - Washington and Lee University, 1931-1942 (Box 50)
      - Washington Document Center, 1946-1947 (Box 50)
      - Washington (D.C.) Public Library
        - 1915-1933 (Box 50)
        - 1944-1945 (Box 50)
      - Washington State College
        - 1923-1924 (Box 50)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 50)
      - Washington University (Seattle)
        - 1907-1941 (Box 50)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 50)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 50)
      - Washington University (St. Louis)
        - 1908-1939 (Box 50)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 50)
      - Water-Soaked Books, 1936-1937 (Box 50)
      - Watkins, Sloan D., 1907-1911 (Box 50)
      - Wayne County Medical Society, 1919-1923 (Box 50)
      - Wayne University
        - 1934-1940 (Box 50)
        - 1942-1950 (Box 50)
      - Weber, Art, 194 (Box 50)
      - Welfare Committee (post-war aid to European librarians) (Box 50)
      - Wellington Public Library, 1923-1928 (Box 50)
      - Wenley, R.M., 1917-1928 (Box 50)
      - Wesleyan College, 1936-1940 (Box 50)
      - West Baden College, 1947-1948 (Box 50)
      - West Virginia University
        - 1908-1943 (Box 50)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 50)
      - Western Michigan College of Education, 1946-1948 (Box 50)
      - Western Ontario University
        - 1920-1924 (Box 50)
        - 1924-1933 (Box 50)
        - 1933-1942 (Box 50)
        - 1945-1950 (Box 50)
      - Western Reserve University
        - 1907-1925 (Box 50)
        - 1928-1935 (Box 50)
        - 1936-1946 (Box 50)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 50)
      - Western State Teachers College, 1922-1935 (Box 50)
      - Western Theological Seminary, 1945-1946 (Box 50)
      - Western Union, 1925-1942 (Box 50)
      - Whimsies, 1920-1921 (Box 50)
      - White, Peter, 1908 (Box 50)
      - White, William A., 1919-1927 (Box 50)
      - Whitney Theatre, 1908-1915 (Box 50)
      - Who's Who in Library Service
        - 1931-1933 (Box 50)
        - 1940-1941 (Box 50)
      - Wichita University, 1928-1934 (Box 50)
      - Wilkes Exploring Expedition Publications, 1933-1934 (Box 50)
      - Williams and Wilkins Company
        - 1919-1925 (Box 50)
        - 1925-1932 (Box 50)
      - Williams College, 1912-1941 (Box 50)
      - Willow Run
        - 1943-1944 (Box 50)
        - 1945-1946 (Box 50)
        - 1946-1947 (Box 50)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 50)
      - Wilmington Institute Free Library, 1908-1927 (Box 50)
      - Wilson, H.W., Company
        - 1906-1916 (Box 50)
        - 1917-1925 (Box 50)
        - 1925-1933 (Box 51)
        - 1933-1942 (Box 51)
        - 1942-1947 (Box 51)
        - 1947-1950 (Box 51)
      - Wilson, Woodrow, 1909 (Box 51)
      - Wisconsin-Michigan Boundary Case, 1925-1937 (Box 51)
      - Wisconsin State Historical Society
        - 1910-1935 (Box 51)
        - 1936-1944 (Box 51)
      - Wisconsin University
        - 1904-1947 (Box 51)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 51)
      - Wise, Thomas J., 1920-1923 (Box 51)
      - Witwatersrand University (South Africa), 1932-1940 (Box 51)
      - Wood, Frank E., 1935-1936 (Box 51)
      - Woodward, A.B., 1914 (Box 51)
      - Worcester, Dean C., 1914-1923 (Box 51)
      - Works, George A., 1925-1927 (Box 51)
      - Works Progress Administration
        - 1935-1936 (Box 51)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 51)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 51)
        - 1938-1941 (Box 51)
        - 1941-1942 (Box 51)
        - 1942-1943 (Box 51)
      - World Almanac, 1949-1950 (Box 51)
      - World Association for Adult Education, 1928-1932 (Box 51)
      - World Federation of Education Associations, 1936-1937 (Box 51)
      - World Peace Foundation, 1928-1935 (Box 51)
      - World Unity Foundation, 1933-1934 (Box 51)
      - Worley, John S., 1925-1927 (Box 51)
      - Worrell, W.H., 1916-1928 (Box 51)
      - Wyer, Samuel S., 1934-1935 (Box 51)
      - Wyoming University, 1912-1930 (Box 51)
      - Yale University
        - 1906-1920 (Box 51)
        - 1920-1930 (Box 51)
        - 1930-1933 (Box 51)
        - 1933-1934 (Box 51)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 51)
        - 1935-1936 (Box 51)
        - 1936-1937 (Box 51)
        - 1937-1938 (Box 51)
        - 1938-1941 (Box 51)
        - 1942-1945 (Box 51)
        - 1945-1950 (Box 51)
        - Press
          - 1910-1922 (Box 51)
          - 1926-1941 (Box 51)
          - 1944-1946 (Box 51)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 51)
      - Yamagiwa, Hanako Hoshino, 1937-1941 (Box 51)
      - Yamagiwa, Joseph K., 1939-1940 (Box 51)
      - Yenching University, 1933-1938 (Box 51)
      - Ypsilanti Work Camp, 1941-1942 (Box 51)
      - Ziwet, A., Estate, 1928-1929 (Box 51)
      - Zoccoletti, Riccardo, 1934-1935 (Box 51)
    - 1950-1957
      The 1950-1957 subseries contains the office files of library directors Rice and Wagman. The materials concerning Frederick Wagman's work with the National Union Catalog (boxes 52 and 75) and the National Library of Medicine (boxes 114-115, 142) are particularly interesting. Wagman's daily diaries for 1953 to 1957 are found in box 126. These diaries served both as appointment books and notebooks in which Wagman recorded brief analyses of the meetings he attended.
      - Accidents, 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - Addresses, A-L (Box 52)
      - Addresses, M-Z (Box 52)
      - Adult Education, 1953-1955 (Box 52)
      - Alabama University, 1954-1955 (Box 52)
      - Alaska University, 1950-1951 (Box 52)
      - American Antiquarian Society, 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - American Association of University Professors, 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - American Book Publishers Council, Inc.
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - American Council of Learned Societies, 1952-1954 (Box 52)
      - American Council on Education
        - 1950-1953 (Box 52)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 52)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - American Library Association
        - 1950-1952 (Box 52)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Board on Acquisition of Library Materials
        - 1954-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Board on Personnel Administration
        - 1951-1953 (Box 52)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - ALA Board on Resources
        - 1952-1953 (Box 52)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 52)
        - 1954-1955, 2 folders (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
        - Subcommittee on the National Union Catalog
          - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
          - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Building Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - ALA Bulletin, 1954-1956 (Box 52)
      - ALA Committee on Intellectual Freedom
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Committee on Relations with Publishers
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Committee on the Margaret Mann Citation, 1954-1958 (Box 52)
      - ALA Conference
        - 1953-1954 (Box 52)
        - 1955 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Cooperative Committee on Microfilming Projects, 1951-1952 (Box 52)
      - ALA Council Steering Committee on the Implementation of the Management Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - ALA Division of Cataloging and Classification
        - 1950-1955 (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
        - Code Revision Committee
          - 1954-1955 (Box 52)
          - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
          - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA International Relations Board
        - 1954-1955 (Box 52)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 52)
      - ALA Joint Committee with F.E.A., 1952-1953 (Box 52)
      - ALA Midwinter Conference
        - 1954-1955 (Box 52)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Reprint Expediting Service, 1955-1957 (Box 52)
      - ALA Serials Committee Roundtable, 1950-1953 (Box 52)
      - American Red Cross
        - 1951-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - Amerika Gedenkbibliothek, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - Amherst College
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 53)
      - Amherst Public Library, 1950-1951 (Box 53)
      - Ann Arbor City Directory, 1955-1957 (Box 53)
      - Ann Arbor Community Chest
        - 1951-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - Ann Arbor High School, 1950-1954 (Box 53)
      - Ann Arbor Library Club, 1950-1954 (Box 53)
      - Annual Report
        - 1950-1951 (Box 53)
        - 1951-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
        - Mailing List, 1953-1954 (Box 53)
        - Suggestions for Improvement and Repair, 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - Appropriations, 1953-1955 (Box 53)
      - Armed Forces Medical Library, 1956-1957 (Box 53)
      - Asia Foundation
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 53)
      - Assistant Director, 1952-1954 (Box 53)
      - Association of American Library Schools, 1950-1952 (Box 53)
      - Association of College and Reference Libraries
        - 1950-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Buildings Institute, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Committee on Audio-Visual Work, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Committee on Interlibrary Loans, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Committee on Library Building Plans
        - 1952-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Committee on Referral of Reference Inquiries, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ACRL Questionnaire
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 53)
      - Association of Research Libraries
        - 1950-1951 (Box 53)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Bibliography, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Cooperative Microfilming Projects, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Interlibrary Lending of Microfilm, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Microfilming of Dissertations, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on National Needs, 1951-1953 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Publication of Dissertations, 1951-1952 (Box 53)
      - ARL Committee on Publication and Recording of Dissertations, 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - ARL Customs Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 53)
      - ARL Farmington Plan
        - 1950-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 53)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - ARL Midwinter Meeting, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - ARL Monticello Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - Associations and Societies
        - 1950-1951 (Box 53)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 53)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 53)
      - Atlantic Union Committee
        - 1950-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 53)
      - Attendance Statistics, Reading Rooms and Study Halls, 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - Ballots: Abandon Stamping Public Catalog Cards, 1955-1956 (Box 53)
      - Bibliographical Society of America, 1950-1954 (Box 53)
      - Bibliographies
        - 1950-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 53)
      - Bishop, William W.
        - 1950-1952 (Box 53)
        - 1952-1955 (Box 53)
        - Lectures, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
        - Short Title Catalogue Checklist (Box 53)
      - Blue Print material (Box 54)
      - Book Budget Requests
        - 1954-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - LSA College, 1954-1955 (Box 54)
      - Book Sale, 1950-1952 (Box 54)
      - Bookplates
        - 1950-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 54)
      - Books Wanted
        - 1951-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 54)
      - Booksellers
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Boston Public Library, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - R.R. Bowker Company, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Bowling Green State University, 1951-1952 (Box 54)
      - Breitenbach, Edgar, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - British Columbia University, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - British Museum
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Brooklyn Public Library, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Brown, Charles H.
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 54)
      - John Carter Brown Library, 1950-1952 (Box 54)
      - Brown University, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Browne, Maurice
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1951-1954 (Box 54)
      - California University
        - 1950-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - California University of Los Angeles
        - 1950-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Calvin College, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - Carnegie Corporation, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1950-1955 (Box 54)
      - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1952-1953 (Box 54)
      - Catalog Cards
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1951-1954 (Box 54)
      - Catholic Library Association, 1950-1954 (Box 54)
      - Central Michigan College
        - 1950-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Chicago Teachers College and City Junior College, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Chicago University
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1951-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
        - Graduate Library School, 1950-1954 (Box 54)
      - Childrens Fund of Michigan, 1950-1953 (Box 54)
      - Christmas Cards, 1956 (Box 54)
      - Cincinnati Public Library, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Cincinnati University, 1954-1955 (Box 54)
      - Clements Library
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
        - Committee of Management
          - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
          - 1951-1952 (Box 54)
          - 1952-1955 (Box 54)
        - Directorship, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - Cleveland Public Library, 1950-1951 (Box 54)
      - Colgate University, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Colorado University, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Columbia University
        - 1950-1952 (Box 54)
        - 1952-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
        - Oral History Project, 1954-1955 (Box 54)
      - Complaints
        - 1950-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Concordia Senior College, 1953-1955 (Box 54)
      - Cornell University
        - 1950-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Council of Europe Committee of Cultural Experts, 1955-1956 (Box 54)
      - Cranbrook School, 1954-1955 (Box 54)
      - Credit Union, 1952-1953 (Box 54)
      - Cresap, McCormick and Paget, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Dartmouth College
        - 1950-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 54)
      - David, Charles, 1955-1956 (Box 54)
      - Debts, 1953-1954 (Box 54)
      - Decimal Classification Committee of Lake Placid Education, 1953-1954 (Box 54)
      - Delaware University, 1952-1953 (Box 54)
      - Denver University, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Deposits, 1950-1952 (Box 54)
      - Detroit News, 1950-1952 (Box 54)
      - Detroit Public Library
        - 1950-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Detroit University
        - 1950-1951 (Box 54)
        - 1956-1958 (Box 54)
      - Devastated Libraries, 1950-1953 (Box 54)
      - Dewey, Harry
        - 1954-1955 (Box 54)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Directories, 1953-1954 (Box 54)
      - Distribution Lists, 1953-1954 (Box 54)
      - Doctoral Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 54)
      - Documents Expediting Project, 1955-1957 (Box 54)
      - Doll, Louis W., 1950-1953 (Box 54)
      - Doubleday and Company, 1955-1956 (Box 54)
      - Dow Chemical Company, 1950-1955 (Box 54)
      - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1956-1957 (Box 54)
      - Duke University, 1950-1955 (Box 54)
      - Eastern College Librarians Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 55)
      - Eastern Michigan College, 1957 (Box 55)
      - Edmonson, J.B., 1952-1953 (Box 55)
      - Edwards, J.W.
        - 1950-1952 (Box 55)
        - 1952-1955 (Box 55)
      - Emergencies, 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1950-1951 (Box 55)
      - English Historical Tracts, List of Duplicates (Box 55)
      - Exchanges
        - 1950-1954 (Box 55)
        - 1954-1957 (Box 55)
      - Exhibits
        - 1950-1951 (Box 55)
        - 1951-1953 (Box 55)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 55)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 55)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 55)
      - Experimental Microphotography, 1950-1952 (Box 55)
      - Faculty Memoranda, 1950-1953 (Box 55)
      - Faculty Research Funds, 1950-1954 (Box 55)
      - Faculty Women's Club, 1954-1957 (Box 55)
      - Far Eastern Bibliographical Project, 1952-1954 (Box 55)
      - F.W. Faxon Company
        - 1950-1952 (Box 55)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 55)
      - Feinberg, Charles E.
        - 1954-1955 (Box 55)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1951-1953 (Box 55)
      - Fellowships in Bibliography
        - Summer Session, 1952 (Box 55)
        - Summer Session, 1953 (Box 55)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 55)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 55)
      - Fine Reports
        - 1950-1951 (Box 55)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 55)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 55)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 55)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 55)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 55)
      - Fisher, Dr. Otto O., 1950-1954 (Box 55)
      - Flint Junior College, 1952-1953 (Box 55)
      - Flint Public Library
        - 1950-1956 (Box 55)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 55)
      - Florida State University, 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Florida University
        - 1952-1954 (Box 55)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Folger Shakespeare Library
        - 1951-1952 (Box 55)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 55)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Ford Foundation Commission on Library Problems, 1954-1955 (Box 55)
      - Ford Foundation Council on Library Resources, 1956-1957
        - Correspondence (Box 55)
        - Minutes (Box 55)
        - Proposals (Box 55)
      - Ford Motor Company, 1951-1953 (Box 55)
      - Ford, Stephen-Serial Slants, 1954-1955 (Box 55)
      - Foreign Periodicals Available on Microfilm, 1952 (Box 55)
      - James Foster Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 55)
      - Freer Facsimiles, 1950-1953 (Box 55)
      - Freer Gallery of Art, 1950-1953 (Box 55)
      - Friends of the Library, 1951-1952 (Box 55)
      - Fukada, Naomi, 1950-1954 (Box 55)
      - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Gandhi Memorial Library Collection, 1950-1953 (Box 55)
      - Gifts
        - 1950-1951 (Box 55)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 55)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 55)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 55)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 55)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 55)
      - Grand Rapids Public Library, 1950-1951 (Box 55)
      - Greeting Cards, 1953-1954 (Box 55)
      - Grolier Society, 1955-1957 (Box 55)
      - Hampshire Inter-Library Center, 1951-1956 (Box 55)
      - Harrassowitz, Otto, 1950-1954 (Box 55)
      - Hartman, Galen C., Bequest, 1951-1953 (Box 55)
      - Harvard University
        - 1950-1954 (Box 55)
        - 1954-1957 (Box 55)
      - Harvard-Yenching Institute, 1950-1952 (Box 55)
      - Haven Hall Fire, 1949-1951 (Box 56)
      - Hebrew University, 1950-1954 (Box 56)
      - Heyworth-Dunne, J., 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - Hobbs, Prof. William H., 1950-1954 (Box 56)
      - Holidays, 1954-1957 (Box 56)
      - Hourly Assistant, 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Hulst, Mrs. Henry, 1950-1953 (Box 56)
      - Human Relations Area Files
        - 1950-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Huntington, Henry E., Library, 1950-1954 (Box 56)
      - Idaho University, 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Illinois Library Association, 1953-1954 (Box 56)
      - Illinois University
        - 1950-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Indiana University, 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - Inquiries
        - 1951-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Interlibrary Loan
        - 1951-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Invitations, 1953-1954 (Box 56)
      - Iowa State College
        - 1950-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Iowa State University
        - 1950-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Jackson High School Library, 1953-1954 (Box 56)
      - Japan National Diet Library, 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Japanese Books, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - Japanese Magazines, 1951-1952 (Box 56)
      - Joffo, David Paul, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - John Crerar Library, 1950-1954 (Box 56)
      - John Hopkins University, 1950-1953 (Box 56)
      - Joint Committee of the Far Eastern Association and the A.L.A., 1951-1952 (Box 56)
      - Joint Committee on Oriental Collections
        - 1950-1951 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 56)
      - Joint Committee on Reproduction of Bibliographical and Reference Works
        - 1950-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 56)
      - Joint Committee on Southern Asia, 1951-1952 (Box 56)
      - Kalamazoo College, 1955-1956 (Box 56)
      - Kalamazoo Public Library, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - Kansas University
        - 1952-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Karpinski, L.C., 1950-1953 (Box 56)
      - Keio University, 1949-1951 (Box 56)
      - Kentucky University
        - 1950-1954 (Box 56)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 56)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 56)
      - Keys
        - 1950-1951 (Box 56)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 56)
        - 1956 (Box 56)
      - Knox College, 1955-1956 (Box 56)
      - Korea University, 1952-1953 (Box 56)
      - Kyoto University, 1951-1952 (Box 56)
      - Labadie Collection
        - 1950-1951 (Box 56)
        - 1951-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1953 (Box 56)
        - 1953-1955 (Box 56)
      - Lakeside Press, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
      - Lawrence College, 1956 (Box 56)
      - Lectures, 1952-1953 (Box 56)
      - Letters of Introduction
        - 1950-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1954 (Box 56)
      - Lewis, Howard B., 1953-1954 (Box 56)
      - Librarian of Congress, 1953-1955 (Box 56)
      - Librarians Wanted
        - 1951-1952 (Box 56)
        - 1952-1955 (Box 56)
        - 1955-1957 (Box 56)
      - Library Buildings